Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things.
That even as the years go by!
Will not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see what sort of
form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're waiting!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look to the wind to dry all the tears!
As you're waving the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
Damn it all!
Where did you go?
This place is like stupid hot.
It's so steamy!
Young, gorgeous, just my type. Woohoo!
She's hot enough to light hell on fire
Wait a minute.
Priorities.
Where's the pansy prisoner
who beat up all the guards?
He's got to be around here somewhere.
Wait, who are you?
Who I am doesn't really
matter right now, lover boy.
Can I get some assistance here?
Can't you see how sweaty I am?
Oh, surely you can help
me out of these rags.
We can do it in here, right? Yep. One sec.
Okay, Chink.
Ladies first.
Oh my, it's dark in here.
No need to be shy.
Where did you run off to?
I'm right here.
This is the worst day ever.
I'll just blame it on
the warden, of course.
I can't believe that a
prisoner outsmarted me.
When do I get to be the warden?
Oh, I use too much poison.
Oh, my tummy.
That's right.
We got the riot shut down.
All of the prisoners have been returned to
their cells and we've retrieved the keys,
but...
I think some are missing.
Damn it. What a pain.
Listen up!
You've got to find him!
He must be somewhere on this floor.
Find him and I'm going to whip the
sass right out of him! Yes, mistress!
Well, you decided to join us, didn't you?
You were sleeping forever. Want a drink?
Brace them for the newcomer,
everyone! Cheers! Cheers!
We've been watching you
guys on our monitor.
Bravo. Quite the show.
I'll seat you.
Where floor did you come from, by the way?
We've got plenty to eat here.
I'd guess you're hungry.
Wait.
Where am I?
Where's Straw Boy?
What?
Do you think you somehow magically
made it out of the prison?
Don't worry.
You're still an impel down, sweetie.
No way! That's a lie!
No one's wearing any prison clothes!
Everyone's drinking and having fun!
Did I wake up in some kind of paradise?
What's the deal? Hold on. I remember.
I was chased down and
attacked by those wolves.
Then Strawboy woke up and helped me.
After that, I passed out.
Then maybe I am dreaming or wait what if
I died from the cold
and I'm in heaven now?
Close but no cigar you've
been sleeping like a
baby out cold for 10 hours
now 10 hours are you?
Kidding me and who are you
my name is Inazuma mind your
manners I'm the one who fetched
you from that A bitter cold,
after all.
You're lucky you two
didn't die from exposure.
Wait, did you say you two?
So you brought Strawboy here, too?
Well, then, where is he?
Speak up! Answer me! Damn you!
There's no time!
Patience, now.
Let him explain things to you.
Him? Who?
Oh, the lights are down! It's time!
The show's starting!
You'll want a Frontier seat.
Did you sleep tight, little candy boy?
Or should I say, little bong boy?
How do you know my name?
Thank you for coming.
Are you ready?
Shaker!
Dixie!
To get here, you have to pass
through the sewers of Impel Down.
Following paths that shouldn't exist.
To a place beyond imagination.
It's a prisoner's paradise.
We've got every pleasure
you could ever beg for.
Right here.
Drinks.
Weapons.
Games.
But most of all.
We have freedom.
Yeah!
You said it!
We got our freedom!
Looks like the jailers are
flipping their tops again.
Prisoners have disappeared.
They've been pulled down into hell.
Those silly little fools
couldn't be more wrong.
We're here and we're queer!
Hmm.
I wouldn't exactly call
this hell, would you?
well who knows maybe it
is but if so at least it's
a gay one the secret
underground where dreams come
true i bid you welcome
to impel down level 5.5
bitches a secret garden for
all All your prisoners, ah,
this is Newcomer-land!
Hee-haw!
They're all queer like me. Yee-haw!
Yee-haw!
I guess I got a little too
excited dancing and cutting loose.
I'm getting dizzy.
Eva, are you all right?
I think I'm going to collapse now.
Then again, maybe I won't.
You were joking.
You sure fooled me.
I made a mistake.
You're Eva the miracle worker, aren't you?
Oh, goodness me.
So you've heard about
little Ongwa, have you?
Hey, watch your mouth.
Show some respect when
you're talking to Eva.
He's royalty, pal.
You've got to bow down before
the Queen of New Karma.
Hail King Eva!
Hush now, my little candies.
I appreciate the admiration,
but don't sweat the small stuff.
I'm not worried about
silly things like labels.
People can call me whatever they like.
They can even call me Dock.
NEVER CALL ME Dock!
Why did you say it?
You've got me again!
Is this really Eva, the Miracle Worker?
The same one that I've worshipped
from afar for oh so many years?
Empire Ivanka!
I've been looking for you.
You were the queen of
Kamabaka Kingdom, weren't you?
About 15 years ago, my father,
who was the king of my homeland,
visited that country of
yours, and then he...
He came back to us as a queen!
Do you have any idea how ashamed I was?
His family and his country were ruined!
I fell for my princely status
and nothing but a lonely pirate!
But all the days I spent suffering
in this living hell are worth it.
If I get one shot at the
monster who destroyed my life?
No please.
Don't do it.
Where did you even get that thing?
Oh no.
Don't point that at me!
Have mercy.
I'm fragile.
If you shoot me with that, I'll die.
You'll kill me?
You can't kill me!
You're such a character!
Oh my goodness!
Yeah!
Huh?
Nuh-uh-uh!
Deathwing!
Huh?
Hell yeah!
That's how we the pats an eye, girl!
How about some death wings?
With just a wink, he was able
to turn back that bullet!
Emporial female hormone!
What was that?
Oh no, what did you chew to me?
You're throwing a fit because your
father wanted to become a woman.
Tell me what's wrong with that?
No, no, no! Stop this!
You wouldn't dare!
Two mothers and one son, two
fathers and one daughter.
What's wrong with that?
You're all family.
Anything but this!
Please, no!
You could become a woman or become a
man, hee-haw, or maybe you could be both.
You should be able to
decide for yourself, right?
That what you call gender is a
label, it's nothing but a border.
I have no need for it, no.
Everyone here is beyond it.
Hee-haw!
We've all crossed over that silly border.
Which means you're looking
at the new human race.
Newcomer!
This is the garden of freedom!
Newcomer land!
Hee-haw!
We have rules!
He turned that guy into a woman!
This is the real deal.
He truly is a miracle worker!
I bid you welcome!
Perhaps you'd like to
join in on the fun now!
Hee-haw!
This is so annoying!
The poor thing's embarrassed!
She's got a long way to go before
becoming a proper citizen of new karma!
Huh?
It's an honor to meet you, Eva.
I never stopped believing
you were still alive.
I'm so glad I found you.
You have no idea.
If you would hear it, I
have a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
My dear friend was poisoned by Magellan.
Can you please save his life?
No antidote can help him.
He's lying there, dying, and
there's nothing I can do.
Please, I'm begging you.
I'll give you my life.
I assume you're talking
about Straw Hat Boy?
Bon Boy.
Hmm?
Did you ever stop to wonder why we
treated your injuries in the first place?
To be quite honest, I didn't notice.
We're all just prisoners down here.
We don't have the means
to simply take in and
care for anyone that we
happen to find injured.
We're not nearly so kind.
You see, I took you in and treated you
because your friend begged me to do it.
Strawboy did what?
He was trying to help me and
got bitten by those wolves.
Please take care of him.
He's my friend.
I can't let him die.
That's not something
just anyone would say.
Not when they're on the verge of death.
I didn't know the flower of friendship
could bloom in a hellhole like this.
But I do know that if I didn't help him,
I'd be no better than
a demon in human guise.
Strawboy!
Anyhow, I already started treatment on
your buddy Strawboy about ten hours ago.
You did?
But it's gonna be rough.
That sounds awful what's
going on in there?
You call this healing
he's been screaming like
this the entire duration
of his treatment but i
Assure you that's part of
the process we've locked
him away for safety this
will last another two
days.
Ten years of your life.
That's what it's going to cost you
if I administer this treatment.
It's a high price, but that
poison is serious Straw Hat boy
Fine by me just so we're clear this
is a high-risk treatment there's
no guarantee that it'll save your
life in your current condition you
have absolutely no chance of survival
the best i could do for you through
this process is increase that chance
to two or three percent what you
face right now is a battle the likes
of which you have never fought before
you must temper that will of yours
to emerge victorious if the poison
wins you will most assuredly die but
if your spirit wins you walk away
it's as simple as that all right
then I wish you a pleasant journey.
To the valley of death, that is.
Emporial healing hormone!
Oh, are you pulling my tail?
Straw boy has been wailing in
agony like that for 10 hours.
Spirit and hormones.
These are the vital
forces of the human body.
Combined, the two bring forth
a tremendous healing potential.
I have drawn out his latent
immunity and changed his
body to enable him to battle
with the deadly poison.
Only time will tell which of
the two of them is stronger.
Within that battlefield
of a body lies destruction
and recovery raging away
at extraordinary speeds.
He will survive only if he
can withstand all that pain.
And escaping from death
does not come cheap.
You can take a look inside
if you really want to
Is there a window?
Straw boy?
How awful!
He's gonna die!
It's gonna tear him apart!
His body will be destroyed
from the inside out!
That wasn't even him in there!
It was a living corpse!
I'm begging you here!
Don't let him suffer like that!
You have to do something, please!
Unlock those chains!
Stop the bleeding and find
a real way to cure him!
Oh, you're the miracle worker, aren't you?
I know he's a mess, but
anything is better than this!
Shut the hell up!
I'm helping him the only way I can!
Don't underestimate
the human will to live!
The what?
Do you have any idea what it takes to
strive against one's own mortality?
To face the ultimate odds?
I'm not a god or an angel
or anything like that.
A miracle worker?
You can call me whatever the hell you
want, but the truth of the matter is this.
I could never save a fool who doesn't
have the will to save himself.
I saved an impoverished
country and a country
that was left in ruin after defeat in war.
But in both cases all I did was
draw out their own spirit to live.
That can only happen to people who
have the courage to keep on fighting.
Making miracles is never easy.
I ate the hornhorn fruit.
It gave me the fabulous power to
alter the hormones of anyone I see.
I can change their sex, body temperature,
skin color, growth, even their emotions.
I can remodel people from the inside
out like an engineer of the human body.
The candy boys and candy
girls you see here have
used my help to really kick
gender in its sorry pants.
Some men became women and some women men.
But all of those hang-ups
are a thing of the past
In short,
those are the kind of miracles we deal in
here I just provide the hormones Ha ha!
Everyone else provides the dream
Oh yeah.
He changed that man from earlier
into a woman by injecting hormones.
I still can't believe that there's a
place like this in the middle of a prison.
I must be dreaming.
It's not a dream, it's a dream man.
All of these candies
you see around here were
once lost prisoners who
made it here by sheer luck,
each with their own story.
See, there are hidden entrances to
Nukamaland on every floor of Impel Down.
You just have to keep an eye out for them.
There's one at the Bloody Mountain of
Needles, one in the Lair of Wild Beasts,
one in the Burning Hellfire.
There's even one in the Mortuary.
We use these handy-dandy
passages to go wherever
we want in this prison to
get everything we need.
A paradise hiding in the bowels
of hell itself why the jailers
would never believe such an
absurdity exists despite living in
our hiding hole we still keep
tabs on everything that's going
on outside we've got a line in
one of the transponder snails the
very same ones the jailers use
that way we're in on all the hip
and horrible happenings here in
the prison we also nab newspapers
from the garbage so we can keep
up with the other parts of the
world and we were Totally tuning
in to Straw Hat Boy's Wild Ride.
It's not every day we
get to see a break in,
a break out, and all sorts
of delectable nonsense.
We were cheering them on the whole way.
But it seems like this place
with yours is gigantic.
Where exactly are we?
Oh, this place wasn't
always here, I assure you.
Some prisoner had a Devil Fruit
power that was good for digging.
They were the first to start
chipping away at these caverns.
They led other prisoners
here a long time ago,
and bit by bit, the new recruits
started building this place together.
To paint a picture,
this paradise of ours is
actually a bit like an
ant farm made from digging
tunnels in the rock.
But to answer your question specifically,
we are located right in
between level 5 and level 6.
Whoa, hang on a minute!
Did you say level 6?
I didn't know there was such a thing!
Well, it's not widely known,
but I assure you it is there.
Level 6 is where the true
villains are kept locked away.
Every one of them is condemned to
a lifetime sentence without parole.
It's known as eternal hell.
Exceedingly wicked crimes are often
covered up by the world government.
As are incidents that would tarnish
the reputation of the powers that be.
You know, like your little rampage that
took you all the way to level four.
If you had tried to pull that
same maneuver a little while back,
it wouldn't have been so easy, by the way.
There was another beastly Betty guarding
this prison not too long ago, you see.
He was the jail manager of
Impel Down, Shiryu of the Reign.
And to size him up, he was just as
strong as Warden Magellan. Honestly,
considering that Magellan spends most
of his time sitting on the crapper,
you might say Shiryu was
twice as troublesome.
As strong as the Warden?
Is that even possible?
Security's not too shabby these days,
but when he was around, it
was downright iron tight.
But you said he's gone now?
What happened?
My job.
The prisoners aren't
here for your amusement.
I remind you that we're
jailers, not butchers.
No one cares about the
lives of these vermin.
I will not tolerate this any longer.
If someone were to find out about
half the atrocities you've committed,
Impel Down would be
disgraced beyond measure.
Now I must exercise my authority as
warden and place you under arrest.
He killed prisoners when and as he
saw fit, even on the slightest whim.
He was completely out of control,
so now they hold him in the darkest corners
of level six as a high-security risk
Unbelievable!
I've never heard of this!
I know it happened before
I got here, but even so!
He's in fine company, too!
Catalina Davon, the world's most
dangerous woman, is down there.
And San Juan Wolf, the great battleship.
Even heavy drinker Vosco Schott.
The names of these criminals are enough
to make anyone tremble with fear.
It's the worst of the worst on
level six half the crimes these
villains committed were so heinous
even the newspapers dared not mention
them your former boss is there too
i suppose he was pretty wild in his
own way mr zero crocodile back in
Alabasta you had quite the little
scuffle with Straw Hat boy didn't
you and look at you now it just goes
to show you that the power of
friendship crosses all boundaries and
there's one of the warlords down
there the first son of the sea gene
bay along with that other guy the
one Straw Hat boy came here to save
second division commander
of the white beard
pirates the fire fist
Portgas d ace i heard
about it over the radio
they're brothers if i'm
not mistaken yes that's
right straw boy said he
only came to impel down to rescue him it's
insane that he thought to
sneak in and miraculous
that he did it um too
bad his plan is dead in
the water now he has to
save himself first which?
unfortunately means that
he's out of time ace
boy is set to be executed
this afternoon at
3 p .m I believe they're going to transfer
him to Navy Headquarters
sometime this morning.
It's already past midnight,
so that means Ace Boy will be taken out
of Impel Down in seven or eight hours,
tops.
Sprawl Boy's treatment is going to
take two more days to run its course.
And even if he survives,
he'll need another three days of
recovery to restore his strength.
So by the time he wakes
up, it'll all be over.
Are you crazy?
He can't take two more
days of that torture!
It's killing him as I
told you his chances are
extremely low will need
a miracle to make it.
He's not the only one that
needs rest you had a rough
run to eat something
nutritious and go back to bed.
So you feel like your old self again.
I have a nice quiet room.
Just perfect for nappy time Screw that
I'm staying with straw boy easy easy.
There's no need little
hope he'll survive anyway
I wonder what he's doing back there.
There's not much he can do, is there?
Hang in there!
You can do it, Strawboy!
I believe in you!
Hang in there!
You can do it!
You've got to be kidding me.
He's been doing that this whole time.
Ha!
Ridiculous.
What's he going to do?
Yell him back alive?
So, you're telling me...
You can't even find
one little twinkle-toe!
Look for him again, you simpletons!
So please Hang in
there Hang in there
You have to live Straw boy
Hang in there Hang in
there Hang in there.
Hang in there.
We believe in you.
Strawboy!
Hang in there.
I just heard some strange news from
the canteen staff on level 5. Huh?
It's about Straw Hat, sir.
He disappeared!
What?
Vice Warden Hannibal, What in
the world are you doing up there?
Listen Ace, that woman, I admit
I don't know anything about her.
But I think it's safe to
assume she's pulling your leg.
So what?
You're just saying she came all the
way down here just to lie to me?
No. Sorry.
I know you mean well.
But honestly, my brother
really would break into here.
He does stupid things without thinking
all the time since we were kids.
He's always been reckless
and made me worry about him.
That idiot!
Yes they've stopped despite how excruciating
the treatment is I fear his silence
brings grim Hidings
a true
pity and
yeti fought valiantly for over 20 hours
Straw boy
He's still alive!
That can't be right!
It made more sense when he was dead!
The hormone treatment
hasn't even gone a day!
Good morning.
Warden Magellan, sir.
It's time for the...
Sorry.
Diarrhea. Please hurry.
I'm afraid it's time for
the transfer of Portgas D.
Ace.
Keep it coming!
This way!
It doesn't matter if it's
cooked or not, just pile it on!
Hurry up!
Just leave it close to him!
Wow.
He's taking in food like his
stomach's made of quicksand.
I thought this guy was tiny!
Where's he put it all?
It's already been 30 minutes, and
he shows no signs to stopping.
Whoa, look at that.
There goes a whole week of food for us.
The boy's got some vitality.
I'll give him that.
He's coming out.
He looks like a monster.
Whoa, that's not natural, man.
Oh, no!
All better!
Let's go!